so
[Music]
that's right
after several hours of waiting i have
acquired
the orange belt
look at that time to add it to the
collection
now only one
more
left
the red one this episode is going to be
insane i have got some crazy
crazy plans and i've even done one of
those crazy plans
before the episode has even started i
have mined out
all of that area and here is the time
lapse to prove it ultra fast speed
[Music]
check it out when we go in here
this is the size of the hall that's
going to be here now i haven't removed
this i'm not going to remove this thing
until the very last second i have been
stockpiling some sugarcane but not
nearly enough for an entire season i can
tell you that much but check it out you
get a real sense of size now the item
sorter will hopefully go in here i may
be able to shave a couple of layers off
here but overall
i am fed up of mining so fed up of
mining but that's not actually going to
be the ow
now that's not actually going to be the
focus of today's episode the base has
been worked on i have done an awful lot
of mining and i mean just to prove how
many materials are all of those chests
are full
full of materials from that excavation
but we're going to take this and we're
going to do something extra special
at the end of last episode i said we
need to do something about this and i've
been saying it for a while
and it's about time we did the thing we
need someone on the server who is in
charge of this diamond pile
and i don't think it should be me i'm
going to campaign for someone to become
the mayor of the shopping district what
can they do well they can do things with
the diamonds i guess
they can pay for roads to be built they
can help laying out they can change the
rules on the pricing and all sorts of
things but it can't just be
anyone it's it's not it's not just gonna
be me i'm i'm the mayor no we need to
have a proper election
so
who do
who
on this server
is the right man for the job well
look at that
mumbo jumbo isn't that isn't that the
face of a man that you would vote for i
have got a fantastic idea now we are
going to campaign for mumbo jumbo to
become the mayor of the shopping
district i mean the the best part of
this is mumbo hasn't hasn't got a clue
he'll find out only when it's too late
in fact it would be absolutely hilarious
if he didn't find out until the very
last second
so the first thing we're gonna do to
kick off our campaign for mumbo jumbo
is a promotional poster now fortunately
there is a space that has already been
allocated
for custom maps people have been making
them for a while now and we are going to
take some not even half of the resources
that we got from here to make this map
so we're going to take shulker box after
shulker box full of stone
and we're going to get cracking on this
i think i've got everything i need now
we just need to head over to that area
this might be the portal yes this looks
like it so
as you can see
this is
not
a small task
in fact
the number of blocks required to make
something like this
will probably astound you
so we're going to take this plot right
here
fortunately cub has already marked out
the exact size for it so that is really
really good
now you can see how many shulker boxes
that i've brought with me but the actual
physical numbers
that have to be placed may really
surprise you i have to place
000 blocks 16 000 that's how big this
space is
and then on top of that i then need to
decorate it to get exactly what i need
so
i think it's not exaggerating to say
this is going to be
awful for me
this is not going to be fun but we are
going to time lapse it and hopefully
this will come out exactly how i hope it
will the campaign begins
vote for mumbo
[Applause]
[Music]
my goodness
look at this that is a lot bigger than
it looks
there there's a lot of placing so here's
the thing i think i've saved some time
of doing this and i'll tell you why cub
has made his newspaper out of snow
blocks here so he had to go and grind
all of these bits of snow
i
didn't have to do that because i already
had all this stone so i've used the
stone but now i need to cover it in snow
and i think the fastest way to do this
is with these guys boom and i can even
remove the pumpkin you sir are going to
help me cover this whole thing
in snow now to stop them going on to
cubs
map i'm gonna make a quick barrier that
goes all the way across because i see
you you're about to go i saw it so
they're going to just slide around
and create more snow hopefully they
don't jump in the ocean but obviously
one snowman isn't gonna cut it so i'm
gonna make a bunch of these guys and
then set them all loose but i think this
will be a lot more fun to watch as
another short time lapse so
let's go
[Music]
so
it is
all complete and it's time for the big
reveal
[Music]
mumbo
for
mare
that looks absolutely fantastic but i've
got to admit it took far longer
and potentially took part of my soul
with it to make it
i think this was eight hours of work for
this
eight hours for one bit of paper the
colors look a little bit different from
the map to what's in sort of reality
this looks quite a lot brighter but i
think overall it looks pretty good i've
added a nice border and a mustache
underneath and you'll notice that the
mustache is actually gone from my face i
basically head butted face planted this
this poster like so
[Music]
and i've put mumbo's well it wasn't even
his mustache the back of mumbo's hair
onto the poster and i'm going to use
this
to promote mumbo for mayor of the
shopping district i find myself just
keep i keep looking at this and i just
like i'm just really happy because
actually building text like this on the
floor
is
surprisingly difficult it doesn't matter
how good you are a building but
writing text in pixels that's tough
so
this is now done and we can actually
start the promotion so let's head over
to the shopping district
but i think i may have got a little bit
ahead of myself
because
even if we did start a campaign
there's just there's just a pile of
diamonds like i really feel that i've
probably gone and done step two before
step one
so maybe we should backtrack a little
bit here and
actually make a building a building
that's like an official thing it doesn't
belong to anyone i don't mind making it
myself but it doesn't belong to anyone
but the shopping district itself meaning
the land that it will be on
doesn't have to be paid for
but it would be like the official place
of the mayor
so i'm thinking what we need is a really
cool townhouse or something like that
like the the not the mayor's house but
you know like his office or something
it's like yeah a townhouse and i have a
vague idea on what to build and there's
actually quite a nice spot here now that
i think about it there's one there as
well
but i'd rather not have to make this
entirely by myself because i have a
feeling it's gonna be quite a big build
the idea i have in mind
so i'm thinking i enlist the help of two
builders on the server and the first two
names that sort of jump out at me are of
course good times with scar my neighbor
and actually potentially bdubs he makes
some really good stuff
so he's he's kind of known for his
building stuff as well so i might drop
them a quick sign at their bases
just asking if they're down to give me a
hand with this thing maybe we'll keep
this secret for now until the town hall
is built because the town hall can then
explain a little bit more about why this
is needed and while we're here we might
as well do the rounds
oh my goodness lots of diamonds the
barge is doing surprisingly well
doesn't look it doesn't look like my new
stock is selling much though we are we
have sold some name tags and we have
sold some golden carrots you know we're
not doing too bad on the diamond front
at the moment i have no idea if ren has
accepted his pesky bird delivery yet i
haven't seen anything so anyway let's go
over to b-dubs is and scar's house let's
start with b-dubs i have no idea where
b-dubs portal is
ah-ha this looks mighty suspect
oh my goodness b-dubs
look at this lovely little village that
he's making yep this is definitely the
right choice b-dubs has a really really
nice style look at those houses he's
even made diorite a feasible block
yeah i really like this i like this a
lot but where do i put the signs to ask
him for help this little visit to
bdubs's place has made me realize how
out of touch i am with anything that's
not in the jungle
and unfortunately for b-dubs
i'm sorry bro
someone took your door and it wasn't it
wasn't me i didn't really know how to
phrase this so i've written this out hi
i'm planning on making a town hall for
the shopping district to promote the
need for a new mayor
hashtag
organize the shopping district
i need some builder help would you be
interested gee ps someone stole your
doors not sure who
so hopefully bdubs will uh get in touch
with me and say that he is interested
and in the meantime i'm gonna steal the
rest of his doors
one
two
three okay i think we're done here and i
think we've definitely made
the right decision oh my goodness look
at these farms
oh this they're purely aesthetic but
just look at that
absolutely amazing
all right let's go before i get insanely
jealous of these builds and now we pay a
little visit to our friend good times
with scar
and this is what happens when you spend
two days making a custom map somewhere
else on hermitcraft you come back and
there are giant trees everywhere
this is gonna this makes the jungle
trees look small
entire jungle with this and iscow's
trees this is gonna put everything right
out of scale
they look amazing anyway where should we
put these signs
probably in larry
as he goes in here all right let's make
the same sort of situation
okay so i've more or less written the
same message asking for help and hashtag
organize the shopping district and p.s
you need a new door
looks like scar is also in need of a
giant item sorter i feel like we're
having a little competition on who can
have the best chest monster
check it out he's got i mean his chest
monster's far more organized than mine
check it out so mine's just out of
render distance but when it comes in
yeah look at that
what a mess this is
which kind of leads me on to my next
project i want to put this to the side
for now until we have the uh the town
hall done
it just makes more sense to me if we
actually have a building showing how
serious i am about this before i start
promoting someone to be mayor so let's
have a look at what this looks like on
an item frame you know what that looks
even better on there than it does in my
hand that looks absolutely fantastic you
can read it from quite a nice distance
as well i'm proper happy with this and
actually speaking of mumbo
i noticed this but i've disabled this
thing but i actually noticed that there
was this thanks we play now
i assume that he's gone for the win he
did he did he went for the win we let
him win
i'm glad i'm glad that he enjoyed it so
gg mumbo
you took the win also thank you for the
diamond
now even though scar and b-dubs haven't
actually given
go ahead i would be surprised if they
said no but i mean they're totally
within their rights but i imagine that
those two are up for anything like that
and i bet secretly they want some
organization for the shopping district
so what i'm gonna do is actually trade a
bunch with my villagers
and i'm going to get
these lots and lots of bricks because i
want to make the shopping district
town hall
mainly out of like bricks granite and
some sandstone and bricks are annoying
to collect so i'm gonna trade them with
these guys
oh they're actually saying hold on hold
on let me fix that
there we go hello hello
okay so i'm going to trade up a little
bit with these guys
and i've got together
quite a lot of bricks and granite this
isn't going to be nearly enough i'm
going to need several okay this is why i
this is why i turn it off
because it does actually hello it does
actually get pretty piercing you know
what i mean with them going like huh huh
you know it kind of like you can tune it
out but when they're shouting hello
hello
you can't you can't tune it out
if i turn them right down
you can still kind of hear them but it's
not quite as bad
so while i prepare
for the shopping district build i think
we'll pop this where no no one should
really be coming in here so we'll pop
this
here for now and we're going to have to
make loads of copies of this to be able
to post it all over the the server but
of course we're going to wait for that
building to be completely finished i
also decided to do a little bit of
tidying up here i got rid of this crane
because it's no longer an accidental
iron farm and there's no need for it so
i've cleaned that up a little bit and
i've also noticed my villagers
have vanished again i don't know what i
i assume that a mob keeps just walking
in here and slaughtering them so i need
to rethink this and ask scar to kindly
send me oh
he's there i wonder if he's seen my
messages look look at him
look at him
he looks so sneaky and a lot of you
might have also assumed that i've
stopped collecting people's doors this
isn't the case this is not the case at
all i am collecting people's doors still
i'm just not hunting for them all the
time i can't spend all day every day
going to each person's house and
stealing their door but when i'm there
when i'm around when i get the
opportunity i add to the collection
and i'm actually getting to the point
where i have
quite a lot of people i mean most of
these are belong to scar but i have
quite a few people's doors now so i'm
thinking as part of this obviously we're
gonna have our item sorter in here
we need the introduction of a door
dungeon of some kind now that's
obviously not gonna happen for quite a
while one we don't have nearly enough
doors
but two
there's not really anywhere to put a
door dungeon in yet because there's no
there's no build
oh hey mr g i want to hear more about
this project
oh looks like we got someone who's in
i'm still just trading away getting up
these bricks heading over now
oh did you
it's just hi
hi
he scared the life out of me
he scared me or should i say he scarred
me
okay i'm gonna call him you genuinely
startled me i was like i'm on my way and
i just turn around and boom you're in
the doorway
oh i was watching you do your training i
didn't want to i didn't want to do this
really
yeah
[Laughter]
wait when when did you did you when you
said can i hear more about this was were
you watching me trading yeah i want to
hear all about your training no you left
me signs in my uh snail yes i did i did
because um i had this idea
to have uh and proper
leader of the shopping district should
we actually head over to the shopping
district so i can pitch you the idea
yes hi scar
hi
i didn't make it to the top i fell
when i said me in the shopping district
this isn't quite what i meant so what
are we here for you're talking about
some town hall business something about
my door so i'm feeling like the shopping
district as beautiful and chaotic as it
is is a little bit of a mess like we got
we've got some cobblestone walkways and
then sometimes we have no walkways and
it's just it's disorder it's chaos and
there's a bee on a leash there is a bee
on a leash like
um there's the chaos
so i was looking at this diamond pile
and i was thinking like no one's in
charge of this and it would make so much
sense if there was a proper mare
and obviously we need to have some sort
of like election we all elect the leader
but there it needs to be more than just
a diamond pile so i'm thinking a big
town hall
and we kind of put the diamonds in there
and then we elect a leader what do you
think oh that sounds really good now
quick question about the mayor would the
mayor be upset because i don't pay for
my land on time for my shops because i
still haven't paid for my land i guess
it depends depends who the mayor is you
know if tango was the mayor he might say
no i'm very upset but if mumbo was the
mayor he'd probably be lenient he'd
probably be okay with it you know what i
mean you know what i mean you probably
won't even notice he's really yeah he
won't even notice exactly
so well i would rather not have to build
this huge building by myself so i've
asked uh you and actually i i sent the
same message to b dubs and i was gonna
be man yeah i was wondering maybe we
could do like a
a collab on it and get all three of us
to make it together kind of share the
burden so we got g-man we got b-man and
s-man that doesn't sound great man
i need i need a new name viewers help me
out but this does sound really
interesting um yeah any idea where you
want to put it this place is absolute
chaos yeah like it's kind of it's
amazing builds but in a horrible
organized fashion
it really drives me crazy if b-dubs is
in we can work that out with him shall
we
yeah that'll be good oh i'm excited
about this this will be
fun i'll be in touch when i hear back
from b-dubs
all right goodbye goodbye
but for now i am afraid that is all we
have time for it has been a very busy
few days
we made the poster for mumbo we mined
out
probably about 20 000 blocks make way
probably more
i mean i this took this took over a day
on its own
but these are the sorts of jobs that
have to be done before you can do the
others
so i'm pretty happy with our progress we
got an orange concrete we made a mere
for mumbo sign and we've asked our
friends to help with the town hall it's
nice to take a little break from
building sometimes especially when
you've got such a monster project like
this but don't worry we'll be back at it
very very soon so thank you very much
for watching everyone i hope you enjoyed
today's episode and i shall see you in
the next episode which
could be extremely exciting
thank you very much for watching and i
shall see you in the next episode good
bye